es24waterdamage.com 2013-05-09

# Privacy Policy - Emergency Services 24 Inc

We are thankful for your faith in us that we will use your information carefully and with sensibility. This notice briefs our privacy policy. When you visit us, you are agreeing to our privacy policy as follows:  

**Personal Information:**

• We collect and store each and every information you enter. For instance, when you give any details such as your name, address, phone number, email-ids, you are not unknown. It depends totally on you not to provide certain information but then you can lose some advantages of our facilities.   
• Every Computer has an Internet Protocol address or the IP address through which the identity of the visitor's Internet service provider are noted. 

**Use of Your Information:**

• As the development procedure of our business, we may buy sell or assets. In the transaction like this, customer information is considered as one of the business assets.   
• If we get a court order to release personal information or account, then we will fulfill the law. If necessary we will also give information regarding the life and safety of others.   

**Protection and Security of Your Information:**  

• Against unlawful disturbance we use the firewall for protecting the information.   
• Access to your information is limited by a “need to know” basis.   
• Complete security is not guaranteed by any system, although we take every important precaution to secure your data.   

**Opt-Out Procedure:**

If you do not desire to receive information from us, at any time after registering, you can send us a request letting us know your new choice.

**Cookies:**  

The alphanumeric cookies are transferred to the hard drive of your computer through your browser, when you visit our site it helps our systems to identify your browser.

**Guidance:**

The products or services are not sold to people under 18. Children may use this site only under parental guidance. 

**Other Website:**

You may find various websites linked from this website. The privacy after making link with another website depends on the privacy policy of that website. All the websites do not provide full security and safety of your information. You can go through the guidelines of online privacy alliance. 

**Contact Us:**

You can contact us to know more about our website and its contents. We have the rights to change any policy in future. The users who are connected to us will get the notice of any change and modifications.
